pintaram.com 2019-05-25

# Privacy Policy - Dailypo

We recognize that your privacy is very important and take it seriously, which is why we developed this privacy policy to explain how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information.

## What is Pintaram?

Pintaram is an advanced Instagram marketing platform, aiming at helping brands, advertisers, and publishers find and explore the latest trends of hashtags, users, photos and videos on Instagram.

## Information Collection and Use

By logging in on Pintaram with Instagram account, you are authorizing us to collect the following info:

  * Access your basic information: Your media & profile info
  * Access your friend lists: Your follower & following lists
  * Access public content: Media & profile info of public users
  * Like photos: Post and delete likes on your behalf
  * Comment on photos: Post and delete comments on your behalf
  * Follow accounts: Follow and unfollow accounts on your behalf

## Links

Our site may contain links to third party websites which may or may not have affiliation with. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. We do not share your personal information with those third parties except as discussed in this document.

## Cookies

Cookies are small files that Pintaram transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow this) that enables Pintaram to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Our cookies are linked to your login information so that you can use Pintaram from your computer throughout the day without logging in each time you visit us.

## Your Choices and Opting-out

We recognize how important your online privacy is to you, so we offer the following options for controlling your ads preference and how we use your data:  
  
You may use the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) opt out tool [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), which will allow you to opt out of seeing personalized ads from NAI approved member companies. Please note that when using the ad industry opt-out tool:  

  * If you use multiple browsers or devices we will additionally opt out those we have linked to you. Since we may not have all your browsers or devices connected back to your user, you may need to execute this opt out on each browser or device.

  * To opt out of receiving targeted ads that are based on your behavior across different mobile applications follow the below instructions, for iOS and Android devices:

    * iOS 7 or Higher: Go to your Settings > Select Privacy > Select Advertising > Enable the “Limit Ad Tracking” setting.

    * For Android devices with OS 2.2 or higher and Google Play Services version 4.0 or higher: Open your Google Settings app > Ads > Enable “Opt out of interest-based advertising”.

Opting out will not prevent you from seeing ads, but those ads will likely be less relevant because they won’t be tailored to your interests. The ads might, for instance, be randomly generated or based on the web page you are visiting.

## Children

Our site is not directed to children under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided Us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at . We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If We become aware that a child under 13 has provided Us with personal information, We take steps to remove such information.

## Terms

Pintaram uses Instagram's data and APIs, please checkout Instagram's Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. Pintaram is dependent on Instagram's API and will work as long as Instagram service is available.

## Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact us at .

## Changes

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review it periodically.
